// Storage of Arith Level 1 Problems
const level1 = [
  { problem: 'ğŸ» + ğŸ»ğŸ» =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ»ğŸ» + ğŸ»ğŸ»ğŸ» =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ»ğŸ»ğŸ» + ğŸ»ğŸ»ğŸ»ğŸ» =', answer: 7 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¼ + ğŸ¼ =', answer: 2 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¼ğŸ¼ + ğŸ¼ğŸ¼ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¼ğŸ¼ğŸ¼ + ğŸ¼ğŸ¼ğŸ¼ =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¢ + ğŸ¢ + ğŸ¢ =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¢ + ğŸ¢ğŸ¢ + ğŸ¢ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¢ + ğŸ¢ğŸ¢ğŸ¢ + ğŸ¢ =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ + ğŸŒ + ğŸŒ + ğŸŒ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸğŸ + ğŸğŸ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸµğŸµğŸµğŸµ + ğŸµğŸµğŸµ =', answer: 7 },
  { problem: 'ğŸµğŸµğŸµ + ğŸµğŸµğŸµ =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ³  + ğŸ³  + ğŸ³ =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒš + ğŸŒš =', answer: 2 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ™ + ğŸŒ™ + ğŸŒ™ =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ ğŸŒ ğŸŒ  + ğŸŒ ğŸŒ ğŸŒ  =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒğŸŒğŸŒğŸŒ + ğŸŒ =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒŒ + ğŸŒŒğŸŒŒ + ğŸŒŒ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒŒ + ğŸŒŒğŸŒŒğŸŒŒ + ğŸŒŒ =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸªğŸª + ğŸªğŸª + ğŸª', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ + ğŸŒ + ğŸŒ =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒŸğŸŒŸ + ğŸŒŸğŸŒŸğŸŒŸ =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ›ğŸŒ›  + ğŸŒ›ğŸŒ› =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ– + ğŸŒ– + ğŸŒ–ğŸŒ– =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ˜ + ğŸŒ˜ + ğŸŒ˜ =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ + ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ + ğŸ›¸ =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ›¸ + ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ + ğŸ›¸ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ + ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ğŸ›¸ =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸš€ + ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸš€ =', answer: 2 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸš€ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸš€ + ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸš€ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸš€ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘©â€ğŸš€ğŸ‘©â€ğŸš€ + ğŸ‘©â€ğŸš€ =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘½ + ğŸ‘½ + ğŸ‘½ + ğŸ‘½ =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘½ + ğŸ‘½ğŸ‘½ + ğŸ‘½ğŸ‘½ =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¤–ğŸ¤– + ğŸ¤– + ğŸ¤– =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¤– + ğŸ¤– + ğŸ¤–ğŸ¤– =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¤–ğŸ¤–ğŸ¤– + ğŸ¤– =', answer: 4 },
];

const level2 = [
  { problem: '0 + 0 =', answer: 0 },
  { problem: '1 + 0 =', answer: 1 },
  { problem: '0 + 1 =', answer: 1 },
  { problem: '1 + 1 =', answer: 2 },
  { problem: '2 + 0 =', answer: 2 },
  { problem: '2 + 1 =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: '3 + 0 =', answer: 3 },
  { problem: '2 + 2 =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: '3 + 1 =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: '1 + 3 =', answer: 4 },
  { problem: '3 + 2 =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: '2 + 3 =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: '4 + 1 =', answer: 5 },
  { problem: '3 + 3 =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: '4 + 2 =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: '5 + 1 =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: '1 + 5 =', answer: 6 },
  { problem: '5 + 2 =', answer: 7 },
  { problem: '4 + 3 =', answer: 7 },
  { problem: '2 + 5 =', answer: 7 },
  { problem: '3 + 5 =', answer: 8 },
  { problem: '4 + 4 =', answer: 8 },
  { problem: '4 + 5 =', answer: 9 },
  { problem: '5 + 5 =', answer: 10 },
];

export { level1, level2 };
